Listen to a teacher talking in a history class.
When people think of life in Europe hundreds of years ago, they often think
of castles built of stone with huge towers, castles with homes of kings, queens
and other powerful people.
Hundreds of relatives，soldiers and workers also lived there.
The kitchen was a very important place in the castle.
It was busy all day and every day.
A castled kitchen was usually located a good distance away from other castle rooms and buildings.
Especially the great hall, a large room, where people gathered for meals and other activities.
This was because of the danger of fires.
The kitchen staff needed to use fire for cooking,
but sometimes kitchen fires accidentally grew out of control and could spread to other
parts of the castle.
That’s why the kitchen was usually far away.
Each kitchen also had a garden, where vegetables were grown.
Back then, food could not be frozen or kept in refrigerators like today.
Some vegetables could be stored underground but not for long.
So most vegetables were picked fresh from the castle garden as they were needed.
But of course, a king’s dinner consisted of many other ingredients like bread, meat and fish.
To prepare a full meal, many cooks were needed.
The castle kitchen employed a whole team of people, some of whom made bread
and others prepared desserts or cooked meat dishes.
The chef was like a head manager,
who was responsible for making sure that the team of assistants did their job right.
Although chefs would also be involved in the cooking of some parts of the
meal.Their main task was to supervise the whole team.